Preliminary Guide to the President’s Advisory Committee on Resources Records (PACOR), 1988-1995
Duke University. University Archives
President’s Advisory Committee on Resources records (PACOR) 1988-1995
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University. President's Advisory Committee on Resources
21.5 linear feet Extent: 21,000 Items
The President's Advisory Committee on Resources was established by President H. Keith H. Brodie in the summer of 1989 following a recommendation of the Academic Council's Task Force on University Governance. Its predecessor was the University Committee on Resources (1988-1989). PACOR was a broad-based committee, chaired by a faculty member, which advised the President on the allocation of the University's financial, human and physical resources. Material includes minutes, reports, handouts, correspondence, memoranda, spiral-bound publications, diskettes, microcassettes and standard cassettes. Materials range in date from 1988-1995.
UA.03.02.0018
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
In off-site storage; 48 hours advance notice is required for use.
Provenance
Materials were transferred over a period of time to the Archives from the President's Advisory Committee on Resources and the office of President H. Keith H. Brodie.
Historical Note
The President's Advisory Committee on Resources was established by President H. Keith H. Brodie in the summer of 1989 following a recommendation of the Academic Council's Task Force on University Governance. Its predecessor was the University Committee on Resources (1988-1989). PACOR was a broad-based committee, chaired by a faculty member, which advised the President on the allocation of the University's financial, human and physical resources. Its twenty-one members consisted of five faculty, seven administrators, two students and seven ex officio non-voting members from the faculty, the administration and the student government. PACOR's chairs were Wes Magat of the Fuqua School of Business, Allen C. Kelley of the Economics Department, and Jim Cox of the Law School. John Wessels served as the staff director until 1995 when his position was eliminated. PACOR continued into President Keohane's administration but with different responsibilities and duties.
Collection Overview
Material includes minutes, reports, handouts, correspondence, memoranda, spiral-bound publications, diskettes (floppy disks), microcassettes and standard cassettes. Materials range in date from 1988-1995.
Subject Headings
Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- Administration -- Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- Finance; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University. Office of Alumni Affairs; Duke University. Office of the Provost; Duke University. President; Cassette tapes; Floppy disks
Related Material
H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records 1963-1984
University Archives. Duke University.
Alumni Affairs Records, 1851-2005.
University Archives. Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- Container List, 25 Boxes
  - Yearly Files 1988/1989, 1989/1990 (Box 1)
    - David Barber (Box 1)
    - Salaries (Box 1)
    - Minutes -- July 12, 1989 - May 7, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Meeting files (Box 1)
    - Academic Incentive Agreements (Box 1)
    - Academic Priorities Committee (Box 1)
    - Adcock, Jack (Box 1)
    - "Adcock letter to Brodie for (Mr. Fitzgerald S.) Hudson" (Box 1)
    - "Adcock's memo on Budgeting" (Box 1)
    - Administrative Services Division (Box 1)
    - Administrative Services Support Units (Box 1)
    - Alumni Affairs and Development (John Piva) (Box 1)
    - Annual Process Cycle (Box 1)
    - Auxiliary Services (Box 1)
    - "Brodie Communications" (Box 1)
    - Budget shortfall (Box 1)
    - Capital Budgeting (Box 1)
    - Center for Jewish Life (Box 1)
    - Communications Div. Report (Box 1)
    - Computing (Box 1)
    - Confidentiality (Box 1)
    - Copy Center and Electronic Publishing (Box 1)
    - Cost Allocation (Box 1)
    - Cost Allocation System Subcommittee (Box 1)
    - Day Care Center (Box 1)
    - Dean's Council (Box 1)
    - Deferred maintenance proposal (Box 1)
    - Deficit -- long-term Department Chairs (Box 1)
    - "Depreciation and Betterments Reserve" (Box 1)
    - "Development office presentation -- John Piva" (Box 1)
    - Discrete Organizational Forecast Units (Box 1)
    - Distribution of faculty, monthly and bi-weekly staff of Duke Univ. (Box 1)
    - Dowell, Earl (Box 1)
    - Duke Univ. Athletic Association [DUAA] (Box 1)
    - DUAA -- correspondence (Box 1)
    - Enrollment (Box 1)
    - Facilities Planning and Management [FP and M] Report (Box 1)
    - FP and M Subcommittee (Box 1)
    - Forecast (Box 1)
  - Yearly Files 1989/1990 cont'd (Box 2)
    - Forecast (Box 2)
    - Forecast Information Responses (Box 2)
    - Forecast presentation, Sept. 7 -- McLamb (Box 2)
    - Forecast data (Box 2)
    - Forecast mailings/handouts (Box 2)
    - FY1991/92 Forecast (Box 2)
    - Forecast procedures (Box 2)
    - Formulas (Box 2)
    - "A Framework for Responding to Calls for Greater Accountability and Productivity" (Box 2)
    - Funding Initiatives [see also New Initiatives] (Box 2)
    - G and A Contributions [General and Administrative] (Box 2)
    - General Ledger System (Box 2)
    - Governance Committee (Box 2)
    - Griffiths, Philip A. (Box 2)
    - Historical data on Budgets (Box 2)
    - Housing (Box 2)
    - "How an Ivory Tower Turns Research into Start-Ups" [Wall St. Journal 9/19/89] (Box 2)
    - Human Resources (Box 2)
    - Indirect Cost Recoveries (Box 2)
    - "Informational" [Budget 1985/86-1989/90] (Box 2)
    - "Informational" [Summary of unrestricted forecasts, budgets and actuals] (Box 2)
    - Investment and Endowment income (Box 2)
    - Investments/E.J. MacDonald (Box 2)
    - Investment Policy Subcommittee (Box 2)
    - John Wessels/Wes Magat proposal on Decentralization of Physical Plant (Box 2)
    - "Letter to Mark Kuhn and Letter from Provost Griffiths [10-89]" (Box 2)
    - Correspondence -- Allen C. Kelley to Wes Magat (Box 2)
    - Libraries [Jerry Campbell -- Sept. 12 presentation] (Box 2)
    - Litigation (Box 2)
    - Mail service (Box 2)
    - Management Issues [newsletter] (Box 2)
    - Material Support (Box 2)
    - Medical School (Box 2)
    - Meetings/agendas (Box 2)
    - Memoranda [from Wes Magat, Chair] (Box 2)
    - Mission Statement (Box 2)
    - New [Funding] Initiatives (Box 2)
    - "PACK"? [computing at Duke Univ.] (Box 2)
    - Parking budget request (Box 2)
    - Planning Office -- Financial Snapshot (Box 2)
    - Provost's Formula (Box 2)
    - Provost's presentation (Box 2)
    - Public Safety (Box 2)
    - Questions for Selected Organizational Units (Box 2)
    - Reports [and letters] to the President (Box 2)
    - Reprographic services (Box 2)
  - Yearly Files 1989/90 cont'd (Box 3)
    - Residence Hall Cost Comparison (Box 3)
    - "Resources Committee" PACOR (Box 3)
    - Salaries (Box 3)
    - Schedules of meetings/memberships (Box 3)
    - Science Resource Initiative [SRI] (Box 3)
    - SRI -- correspondence (Box 3)
    - Staffing data (Box 3)
    - Stores operation (Box 3)
    - Student Affairs (Box 3)
    - Tel-Com (Box 3)
    - Summary of Transit System Upgrade (Box 3)
    - Summary of Unrestricted Forecasts, Budgets and Actuals (Box 3)
    - Tuition (Box 3)
    - Uninsured Litigation/Risk Fund (Box 3)
    - Vending Machines (Box 3)
    - Year-End Appropriations (Box 3)
    - Year-End Funding (Box 3)
    - Year-End Surplus (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Yearly Files, 1990/1991 (Box 3)
    - Minutes -- Sept. 18, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Meeting files (Box 3)
    - Academic Priorities Committee (Box 3)
    - Academic Enhancements (Box 3)
    - Jack Adcock -- correspondence/memoranda (Box 3)
    - "Adcock on Financial indicators" (Box 3)
    - Agency for International Development seminar [A. Kelley] (Box 3)
    - Annual Giving (Box 3)
    - 1990-1991 Annual Report (Box 3)
    - Biodesign Building Project (Box 3)
    - President Brodie -- correspondence (Box 3)
    - "Budget cutting, streamlining" article [Stanford Observer, April-May 1990] (Box 3)
    - Capital Budget (Box 3)
    - Compensation Management Report (Box 3)
    - Compensation Survey (Box 3)
    - Computing Cost Accounting (Box 3)
    - Deferred Maintenance/Capital Reminants (Box 3)
    - Earl Dowell (Box 3)
    - Duke Endowment (Box 3)
    - Duke University Management Company [DUMAC] (Box 3)
    - Enrollment (Box 3)
    - Duke University Facilities Audit (Box 3)
    - Facilities Planning and Management (Box 3)
    - Financial Aid (Box 3)
  - Yearly Files 1990/1991 cont'd (Box 4)
    - Financial Statements and Reports (Box 4)
    - Forecast (Box 4)
    - Forecast 1991/92 (Box 4)
    - Forecast and Budget (Box 4)
    - Formulas -- master plan (Box 4)
    - Formulas -- chart (Box 4)
    - Formulas -- correspondence (Box 4)
    - Formulas -- letter of transmittal [draft] (Box 4)
    - Formula system (Box 4)
    - Funding Initiatives (Box 4)
    - General Fund (Box 4)
    - The Graduate School (Box 4)
    - "Harvard Visit by John (Wessels)," April 1991 (Box 4)
    - Health Care Committee (Box 4)
    - Housing (Box 4)
    - Incremental Tuition Revenue (Box 4)
    - Investment Policy Subcommittee (Box 4)
    - Investments (Box 4)
    - Allen Kelley -- Dorm Deferred Maintenance (Box 4)
    - Allen Kelley -- Building Manager Proposal (Box 4)
    - Thomas Langford (Box 4)
    - Wes Magat, chair (Box 4)
    - Maintenance Deficiency Funding Proposal (Box 4)
    - Management Center Budget and Formula Proposal (Box 4)
    - Meeting agendas (Box 4)
    - Mid-Year report for 1990-91 (Box 4)
    - PACOR bills, 1989-1991 (Box 4)
    - Provost Search Committee (Box 4)
    - Charles Putman (Box 4)
    - SRI (Box 4)
    - Siemer Energy Committee (Box 4)
    - Siemer report on Facilities Planning and Management (Box 4)
    - Spending policy (Box 4)
    - Summer Session (Box 4)
    - Tax-Free Bonding Controversy (Box 4)
    - Triangulation Experiment (Box 4)
    - University Financial Aid Programs report (Box 4)
    - Undesignated Gift, Grant and Contract Income (Box 4)
    - University Operations (Box 4)
    - Utilization of Classroom Facilities during the Academic Year (Box 4)
    - John Wessels (Box 4)
  - Yearly Files, 1991/1992 (Box 4)
    - Minutes -- September 11, 1991 - April 29, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Meeting files (Box 4)
  - Yearly Files 1991/1992 cont'd (Box 5)
    - Academic and Financial Planning (Box 5)
    - ACCRA cost of living index (Box 5)
    - Jack Adcock (Box 5)
    - Adjusting Faculty Salaries for the Cost of Living (Box 5)
    - Budget (Box 5)
    - Auxiliaries (Box 5)
    - Auxiliaries -- staffing (Box 5)
    - Auxiliaries -- transportation (Box 5)
    - President Brodie (Box 5)
    - Analysis of Year-End Budget Surpluses (Box 5)
    - Budget trends (Box 5)
    - FY92/93 Budget Highlights (J.Adcock's presentation) (Box 5)
    - Paula Burger -- correspondence (Box 5)
    - Capital Projects Subcommittee report (Box 5)
    - Central Administrative Costs of 1991-1992 Budget (Box 5)
    - Compensation Committee (Box 5)
    - Competitive Bidding (Box 5)
    - Development Presentation (Box 5)
    - Dorms and Capital Projects Committee (Box 5)
    - Duke Endowment Gifts (Box 5)
    - DUAA Budgets -- Summary FY91/92 (Box 5)
    - DUMAC (Box 5)
    - East Campus Reviews and Planning (Box 5)
    - Environment, pending (Box 5)
    - Energy Conservation Advisory Committee [and Feb.92 report to PACOR] (Box 5)
    - Facilities Planning and Management -- Internal Audit (Box 5)
    - Financial Aid (Box 5)
    - Forecast (Box 5)
    - Forecast -- correspondence (Box 5)
    - Forecast -- Forecasting procedures and Strategic issues (Box 5)
    - Forecast -- possible candidates for FY91/92 revision (Box 5)
    - Forecast -- University Forecast/Master formula (Box 5)
    - "Pending -- Formula system" (Box 5)
    - Formula -- Master Formula subcommittee (Box 5)
    - "Formlua/Budget/Forecast subcommittee -- Hillerbrand" (Box 5)
    - Governing Principles for Provost's area interim formula (Box 5)
    - Graham, John [Planning Office Director] (Box 5)
    - Harvard Yard Fence Restoration (Box 5)
    - Allen C. Kelley (Box 5)
    - Kuniholm, Bruce -- Policy Sciences Building (Box 5)
    - Law School Presentation -- Pamela Gann (Box 5)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee [Bd. of Trustees] -- January 1992 Planning Document (Box 5)
    - Market Interest Rates (Box 5)
    - Meeting agendas (Box 5)
    - Nomination letters (Box 5)
    - Office Services Division (Box 5)
    - Personnel report -- John Wessels (Box 5)
    - Pietrantoni, Joe -- Report on FTE analysis (Box 5)
    - Pietrantoni, Joe -- Session on Planning (Box 5)
    - Procurement Marshall Report (Box 5)
    - Provost's Formula Agreement (Box 5)
    - Provost's Interim Area Formula (Box 5)
    - Provost Master Budget Incentive Agreement (Box 5)
    - Report for 1991/92 academic year (Box 5)
    - Residential Life (Box 5)
    - Resolution on Human Resources [draft] (Box 5)
    - Salaries and tuition (Box 5)
  - Yearly Files 1991/1992 cont'd, 1992/1993, 1993/1994 (Box 6)
    - Strategic Plans for Information Systems at Duke [July 1991 report] (Box 6)
    - Student Employees Analysis (Box 6)
    - Suggested Rules (Box 6)
    - Total Compensation Committee (Box 6)
    - Tax-exempt bonds (Box 6)
    - Tax-free bonds (Box 6)
    - Managing Tax-free bonds (Box 6)
    - Undergraduate Enrollment (Box 6)
    - Roy Weintraub [Academic Council, chair] on Enrollments (Box 6)
    - Year-Round Education at Duke: A Summary of Relevant Issues (Box 6)
    - Minutes -- September 2, 1992 - April 21, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Meeting files (Box 6)
    - Forecast (Box 6)
    - Forecast -- adjustment recommendations (Box 6)
    - Master Formula subcommittee (Box 6)
    - PACOR Planning and Pending (Box 6)
    - Worker's Compensation (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous material [incl. University Forecast material] (Box 6)
    - Minutes -- September 8, 1993 - June 16, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Meeting files [11/3/93 meeting] (Box 6)
    - Capital Planning and Budgeting Project (Box 6)
  - Yearly Files 1993/1994 cont'd, 1994/1995 (Box 7)
    - "Capital projects at Duke: Priority Setting, Approval Process, and Budgeting Procedures" (Box 7)
    - Tuition policies (Box 7)
    - Minutes -- August 31, 1994 - May 17, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Agendas, Meetings, etc. (Box 7)
    - Managed Care (Box 7)
    - Recreation and Fitness Facilities (Box 7)
  - Subject Files
    - Academic Areas, 1989-1991 [incl. Provost's 9/19/89 presentation] (Box 7)
    - Accounting Systems, 1988-1990 (Box 7)
    - Administrative Services, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Agendas 1989-1992 (Box 7)
    - DUAA 1990 (Box 7)
    - Auxiliary Services 1988-1992 (Box 7)
    - Board of Trustees/Strategic Planning/Feasibility Study, 1994 [miscellaneous material] (Box 7)
    - Copy Center (Box 7)
    - Correspondence 1988-1994 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, July 1990 - October 1992 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, October 1992 - September 1993 (Box 7)
    - Cost Accounting Subcommittee, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Facilities Planning and Management, 1987-1990 (Box 8)
    - FP and M, 1989-1992 (Box 8)
    - FP and M -- Energy Management Control System (Box 8)
    - FP and M -- "Outrageous," 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - FP and M -- Proposal for Enhancing the FP and M Function at DU, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Financial Aid 1991-1992 (Box 8)
    - Forecast, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
    - Forecast Information Responses, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Formula Schools, 1989-1991 (Box 8)
    - Funding Initiatives, 1990-1992 (Box 8)
    - G and A expenses, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - Gift income/Annual giving, 1989-1992 (Box 8)
    - Harvard University, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - Indirect cost revenues, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
    - Information systems, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - Internal Audit Office, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
    - Investment and Endowment Income, 1989-1993 (Box 8)
    - Key Documents (Box 9)
    - Libraries, 1989-1991 (Box 9)
    - Medical Center, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
    - Plant Funds, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
    - Recycled Bond funds, 1991-1994 (Box 9)
    - PACOR recommendations, 1989-1993 (Box 9)
    - Reports, 1990-1994 [incl. Annual Reports] (Box 9)
    - SRI, 1989-1994 (Box 9)
    - Staffing, 1989-1992 (Box 9)
    - Student Affairs, 1989-1993 (Box 9)
    - Summer Projects, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
    - Uninsured risk/Litigation fund, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
    - Year-end appropriations, 1990-1992 (Box 9)
    - Year-round operations, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Working Files -- Box List (Box 10)
    - Working Files 1992/1993 (Box 10)
    - Forecast 1993/1994 (Box 10)
    - FP and M Subcommittee, Spring 1990 (Box 10)
    - PACOR office records -- accounting (Box 10)
    - Membership and distribution lists (Box 10)
  - 1994 University Strategic Planning Committee ["Shaping Our Future"; includes minutes, email, reports, school summaries for the Board, and other material] Board of Trustees Committee on Institutional Advancement, Feb. 1995 (Box 11)
  - FP and M report, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Working/Subject Files 1989/1990 [formulas; cost allocation; computing; DUAA; Alumni Affairs; Endowment, Earnings] (Box 11)
  - Budget process -- Princeton, 1988 (Box 12)
  - University Committee on Resources, 1988-1989 [predecessor to PACOR] (Box 12)
  - 1989 Child Care Proposal (Box 12)
  - DukeNet Proposal (Box 12)
  - 2 Financial Aid reports for 1991 [duplicate] and 1992. (Box 12)
  - Working/Subject Files [Student Affairs 1992; FP and M; Computing; Forecast 1992/93] (Box 12)
  - Business and Finance Committee Volumes (Box 13)
    13 spiral-bound volumes [12 and 1 duplicate] detailing operations of the Business and Finance Committee of the Board of Trustees -- dating from November 6, 1988-March 28, 1993. Contain information prepared for meetings of the B and F Committee.
  - Other Volumes (Box 14)
    Volumes: Duke University FY 1990/91 Budget; Actual Financial Operations FY 1898/90, 1990/91 [2 vol.]; Forecast 1989/90 and 1990/91; Administrative Services Division FY1990/91 Analysis; Wiley and Wilson Sewer System and Steam Distribution Studies, 1990-1991 [3 vol.]; Project Nexus [future of computing at Duke], 1989; Strategic Plans for Information Systems, 1991; Facilities Audit, 1990.
  - Subject Files (Box 14)
    Working/Subject Files [Energy Conservation, 1994; Heating Plant Task Force report; Infrastructure Summary report, 1992; Ad Hoc Committee on Formulas, Fall 1990; Formula Proposal, Fall 1990; Forecast, March 1990; 1991 Long-range Planning report titled "Strategic Issues in the 90s"]
  - Alumni Affairs and Development, 1990-1995 (Box 15)
    Records include Carol O'Brien Associates Report on Development, 1995; 1994 draft of strategic plan for the Law School; minutes of the Alumni Affairs and Development [AA and D] Cabinet, 1994-1995; reports of various AA and D Task Forces, 1994, including materials on Duke Seminar planning; strategic plans for AA and D and the Alumni Association, 1993; and Operating Plans for AA and D from 1991-1994.
  - Working Files, c. 1993-1995 (Box 16)
    1995 PACOR review of DUMAC; 9/14/94 report to PACOR, "Recreation Facilities and Cameron Annex Project" [dup.]; fund-raising publications from other institutions and from Council for Advancement and Support of Education; drafts of strategic plans for Arts and Sciences [1994], School of Engineering [1994?], Divinity School [1993], and Fuqua School of Business [1994].
  - Working Files, ca. 1988-1993 (Box 17)
    Some records of the President's Committee on Health Care [1990, chaired by Jim Cox] and 1992 Strategic Planning Committee [Cox served]. PACOR subjects include Capital Projects Subcommittee; fundraising and development; strategic plans, 1992; planning initiatives at Princeton; 1988 report of Parking and Traffic Task Force; and the Chancellor's Committee on Year-Round Education.
  - Reports, c. 1989-1995 (Box 18)
    1992-93 Compensation Management Report; 1990 Facilities Audit; President's Committee on Health Care, 1990-1991; 1992 Forecast Information; University Financial Snapshot -- Projections for 1990-1995 and 1991-1996; 1992 Residential Hall Communications Cabling [GTE]; and revenue trial balances and one line summaries, FY89/90 and 90/91 [4 vol.].
  - Bound Computer Printouts (Box 19 and 22)
    [labeled "Confidential]: Allocated and restricted funds with activity, [FY89/90] and Allocated and restricted funds with limited activity, FY 89/90. Tapes of meetings -- micro and standard cassettes Diskettes 3.5"Enter scope/content note.
  - Resources Committee, University, 1988 Apr.-1989 Apr. 30 (Box 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1989 May 1-1989 July 31 (Box 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1989 Aug. 1-1989 Sept. 30 (Box 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1989 Oct. 1-1989 Oct. 31 (Box 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources: Documents for meetings, 1989 Oct. 5, 1989 Oct. 10 (Box 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1989 Nov. 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1990 Jan. 1-1990 Mar. 30 (Box 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1990 Apr. 1-1990 Aug. 30 (Box 20)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1990 Sept. 1-1990 Dec. 31 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1991 Jan. 1-1991 Apr. 30 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1991 May 1-1991 Oct. 31 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1991 Nov. 1-1991 Dec. 31 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1992 Jan. 1-1992 May 31 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1992 June 1-1992 Sept. 30 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1992 Oct. 1-1992 Dec. 31 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1993 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1993 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 21)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Resources, 1993 Jan. 1-1993-June 30 (Box 23)
  - Public Safety Report to the Advisory Committee on Resources (Box 24)
  - Facilities Planning and Management Report to the Advisory Committee on Resources (Box 24)
  - Communications Division Report to the Advisory Committee on Resources (Box 24)
  - Material Support Report to the Advisory Committee on Resources (Box 24)
  - Human Resources Report to the Advisory Committee on Resources (Box 24)
  - Auxiliary Services Report to the Advisory Committee on Resources (Box 24)
  - Academic Plan, Duke University Working Draft, volume 1, 1987 September 12 (Box 24)
  - Recreation Facilities and Cameron Annex Project, 1994 September 14 (Box 24)
  - Report to PACOR, University Financial Aid Programs, 1991 April 10 (Box 24)
  - Strategic Plans for Information Systems at Duke, 1991 July (Box 24)
  - Cassette tapes of PACOR meetings, micro and standard size, 1990-1993 (Box 25)